{"uuid": 0, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49087820_0_461228320225084868_Currency:Alphabetic code", "label": "Alphabetic code", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49087820_0_461228320225084868_Currency", "desc": "ISO 4217 currency designators.", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "currency code : ISO 4217 currency designators.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Alphabetic code . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 1, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49087820_0_461228320225084868_Currency:Numeric code", "label": "Numeric code", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49087820_0_461228320225084868_Currency", "desc": "Superproperty for any designation (string, integer as string) that is meant to identify an entity within the context of a system", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "code : Superproperty for any designation (string, integer as string) that is meant to identify an entity within the context of a system", "input_prompt": "Column name: Numeric code . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 2, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49087820_0_461228320225084868_Currency:Symbol", "label": "Symbol", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49087820_0_461228320225084868_Currency", "desc": "HUGO Gene Symbol", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "Symbol : HUGO Gene Symbol", "input_prompt": "Column name: Symbol . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 3, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:84548468_0_5955155464119382182_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:84548468_0_5955155464119382182_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 4, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:84548468_0_5955155464119382182_Film:Director(s)", "label": "Director(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:84548468_0_5955155464119382182_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 5, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49801939_0_6964113429298874283_Mountain:HEIGHT IN METERS", "label": "HEIGHT IN METERS", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49801939_0_6964113429298874283_Mountain", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: HEIGHT IN METERS . [SEP] Other column names: MOUNTAIN | HEIGHT IN METERS | RANGE | CONQUERED ON . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 6, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:73988811_0_2775758476756716904_Film:Director(s)", "label": "Director(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:73988811_0_2775758476756716904_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Director(s) | Released | Rating | View Date | Amazon . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 7, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:73988811_0_2775758476756716904_Film:Released", "label": "Released", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:73988811_0_2775758476756716904_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Released . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Director(s) | Released | Rating | View Date | Amazon . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 8, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:64499281_8_7181683886563136802_Museum:Stadt", "label": "Stadt", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:64499281_8_7181683886563136802_Museum", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Museum", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Stadt . [SEP] Other column names: RANG | Museum | Stadt | Facebook-Fans . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 9, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:58891288_0_1117541047012405958_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:58891288_0_1117541047012405958_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 10, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:58891288_0_1117541047012405958_Film:Director(s)", "label": "Director(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:58891288_0_1117541047012405958_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 11, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:48944826_0_2321751364268052533_VideoGame:Genre", "label": "Genre", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:48944826_0_2321751364268052533_VideoGame", "desc": "The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "genre : The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Genre . [SEP] Other column names: Cover | Status | Name | Genre | FSK | Kommentar | Verliehen? | System . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 12, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:48944826_0_2321751364268052533_VideoGame:System", "label": "System", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:48944826_0_2321751364268052533_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: System . [SEP] Other column names: Cover | Status | Name | Genre | FSK | Kommentar | Verliehen? | System . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 13, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:43237185_1_3636357855502246981_Scientist:Granting Institution", "label": "Granting Institution", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:43237185_1_3636357855502246981_Scientist", "desc": "schools that they attended", "table_name": "Scientist", "groundtruth_response": "alma mater : schools that they attended", "input_prompt": "Column name: Granting Institution . [SEP] Other column names: Mathematician | Year of PhD | Granting Institution | Supervisor | Thesis . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 14, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:90325533_0_6668263142989366843_Hospital:Ashton-under-Lyne", "label": "Ashton-under-Lyne", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:90325533_0_6668263142989366843_Hospital", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Hospital", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Ashton-under-Lyne . [SEP] Other column names: Tameside General Hospital | Breast Care Unit | Ashton-under-Lyne . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 15, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:86747932_0_7532457067740920052_Airline:1T", "label": "1T", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:86747932_0_7532457067740920052_Airline", "desc": "IATA designation for airline companies", "table_name": "Airline", "groundtruth_response": "IATA code : IATA designation for airline companies", "input_prompt": "Column name: 1T . [SEP] Other column names: 1T | 1Time | WebCheckIn | Reisegep\ufffdck . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 16, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21801207_0_8144839668470123042_VideoGame:Developer", "label": "Developer", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21801207_0_8144839668470123042_VideoGame", "desc": "Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "developer : Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Developer . [SEP] Other column names: LW | TW | Title | Developer | Label | Publisher . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 17, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21801207_0_8144839668470123042_VideoGame:Label", "label": "Label", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21801207_0_8144839668470123042_VideoGame", "desc": "Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "developer : Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Label . [SEP] Other column names: LW | TW | Title | Developer | Label | Publisher . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 18, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21801207_0_8144839668470123042_VideoGame:Publisher", "label": "Publisher", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21801207_0_8144839668470123042_VideoGame", "desc": "Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "publisher : Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "input_prompt": "Column name: Publisher . [SEP] Other column names: LW | TW | Title | Developer | Label | Publisher . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 19, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:9206866_1_8114610355671172497_Country:GNI", "label": "GNI", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:9206866_1_8114610355671172497_Country", "desc": "is a measure of the inequality of a distribution. It is commonly used as a measure of inequality of income or wealth.", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "gini coefficient : is a measure of the inequality of a distribution. It is commonly used as a measure of inequality of income or wealth.", "input_prompt": "Column name: GNI . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Region | Income | GNI | Population . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 20, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:38428277_0_1311643810102462607_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:38428277_0_1311643810102462607_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 21, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:38428277_0_1311643810102462607_Film:Director(s)", "label": "Director(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:38428277_0_1311643810102462607_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 22, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:40844462_1_6230938203735169234_Film:Rel.", "label": "Rel.", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:40844462_1_6230938203735169234_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Rel. . [SEP] Other column names: Movie | Rel. | Director | Reviewed . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 23, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:40844462_1_6230938203735169234_Film:Director", "label": "Director", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:40844462_1_6230938203735169234_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director . [SEP] Other column names: Movie | Rel. | Director | Reviewed . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 24, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:54773498_0_4341462266113591159_Building:Meters", "label": "Meters", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:54773498_0_4341462266113591159_Building", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Building", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: Meters . [SEP] Other column names: Name | City | Country | Meters | Feets | Pictures . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 25, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:54773498_0_4341462266113591159_Building:Feets", "label": "Feets", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:54773498_0_4341462266113591159_Building", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Building", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: Feets . [SEP] Other column names: Name | City | Country | Meters | Feets | Pictures . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 26, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_4_1832350971585698643_Country:Government", "label": "Government", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_4_1832350971585698643_Country", "desc": "broadly, the type of structure of its government", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "government type : broadly, the type of structure of its government", "input_prompt": "Column name: Government . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Date | Previous Names | Capital | Government | Languages . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 27, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_4_1832350971585698643_Country:Languages", "label": "Languages", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_4_1832350971585698643_Country", "desc": "Use dc:language for literal, language for object", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "language : Use dc:language for literal, language for object", "input_prompt": "Column name: Languages . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Date | Previous Names | Capital | Government | Languages . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 28, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:44206774_0_3810538885942465703_GolfPlayer:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:44206774_0_3810538885942465703_GolfPlayer", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "GolfPlayer", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Winner/2nd | Scores | Total | Money (US$) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 29, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:32051842_5_1757891723986774036_Museum:Stadt", "label": "Stadt", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:32051842_5_1757891723986774036_Museum", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Museum", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Stadt . [SEP] Other column names: RANG | Museum | Stadt | Facebook-Fans . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 30, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:3962429_0_3452614694863053249_Hotel:Address", "label": "Address", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:3962429_0_3452614694863053249_Hotel", "desc": "Address of something as literal. Usually Building, but we also use it for the address of a Region's or Settlement's government", "table_name": "Hotel", "groundtruth_response": "address : Address of something as literal. Usually Building, but we also use it for the address of a Region's or Settlement's government", "input_prompt": "Column name: Address . [SEP] Other column names: Number | IDF Host Hotels | Address | IDF 2011 Group Rate | Rewards Program | Approximate Distance from Moscone West . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 31, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:69381058_0_984708047398578866_Mountain:8.848", "label": "8.848", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:69381058_0_984708047398578866_Mountain", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: 8.848 . [SEP] Other column names: Everest | 8.848 | Nepal/Tibet | Asia . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 32, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:69381058_0_984708047398578866_Mountain:Asia", "label": "Asia", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:69381058_0_984708047398578866_Mountain", "desc": "links a country to the continent it belongs", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "continent : links a country to the continent it belongs", "input_prompt": "Column name: Asia . [SEP] Other column names: Everest | 8.848 | Nepal/Tibet | Asia . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 33, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:19361188_0_1640726405141876003_Mountain:Height (m)", "label": "Height (m)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:19361188_0_1640726405141876003_Mountain", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: Height (m) . [SEP] Other column names: Summit | Height (m) | Height (ft) | Grid Reference | Date . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 34, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:19361188_0_1640726405141876003_Mountain:Height (ft)", "label": "Height (ft)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:19361188_0_1640726405141876003_Mountain", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: Height (ft) . [SEP] Other column names: Summit | Height (m) | Height (ft) | Grid Reference | Date . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 35, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:12125836_0_1134348206297032434_RadioStation:Format", "label": "Format", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:12125836_0_1134348206297032434_RadioStation", "desc": "The programming format describes the overall content broadcast on a radio or television station.", "table_name": "RadioStation", "groundtruth_response": "programme format : The programming format describes the overall content broadcast on a radio or television station.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Format . [SEP] Other column names: Dial Location | Call Letters | Format | Address | Telephone . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 36, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:12125836_0_1134348206297032434_RadioStation:Address", "label": "Address", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:12125836_0_1134348206297032434_RadioStation", "desc": "Address of something as literal. Usually Building, but we also use it for the address of a Region's or Settlement's government", "table_name": "RadioStation", "groundtruth_response": "address : Address of something as literal. Usually Building, but we also use it for the address of a Region's or Settlement's government", "input_prompt": "Column name: Address . [SEP] Other column names: Dial Location | Call Letters | Format | Address | Telephone . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 37, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:97941125_0_8220652154649529701_Currency:Alphabetic code", "label": "Alphabetic code", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:97941125_0_8220652154649529701_Currency", "desc": "ISO 4217 currency designators.", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "currency code : ISO 4217 currency designators.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Alphabetic code . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 38, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:97941125_0_8220652154649529701_Currency:Numeric code", "label": "Numeric code", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:97941125_0_8220652154649529701_Currency", "desc": "Superproperty for any designation (string, integer as string) that is meant to identify an entity within the context of a system", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "code : Superproperty for any designation (string, integer as string) that is meant to identify an entity within the context of a system", "input_prompt": "Column name: Numeric code . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 39, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:97941125_0_8220652154649529701_Currency:Symbol", "label": "Symbol", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:97941125_0_8220652154649529701_Currency", "desc": "HUGO Gene Symbol", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "Symbol : HUGO Gene Symbol", "input_prompt": "Column name: Symbol . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 40, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:24417511_0_3058323105166963431_BaseballPlayer:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:24417511_0_3058323105166963431_BaseballPlayer", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "BaseballPlayer", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Voted By | Inducted As | Votes | % of Ballots . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 41, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:9686394_0_5980699488362107028_Airport:State", "label": "State", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:9686394_0_5980699488362107028_Airport", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Airport", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: State . [SEP] Other column names: Code | Airport Name | City | State . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 42, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:25404227_0_2240631045609013057_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:25404227_0_2240631045609013057_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 43, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:25404227_0_2240631045609013057_Film:Director(s)", "label": "Director(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:25404227_0_2240631045609013057_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 44, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:71840765_0_6664391841933033844_Lake:water gauge", "label": "water gauge", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:71840765_0_6664391841933033844_Lake", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Lake", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: water gauge . [SEP] Other column names: Lake | water temperature | water gauge . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 45, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49772588_0_6549847739640234347_Country:Dioceses", "label": "Dioceses", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:49772588_0_6549847739640234347_Country", "desc": "A religious administrative body above the parish level", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "diocese : A religious administrative body above the parish level", "input_prompt": "Column name: Dioceses . [SEP] Other column names: # | Catholics | Population | Percent Catholic | Country | Dioceses | Diocesan Priests | Religious Priests | Total Priests | Permanent Deacons | Male Religious | Female Religious | Parishes . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 46, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:88732174_0_7321365014357502211_BaseballPlayer:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:88732174_0_7321365014357502211_BaseballPlayer", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "BaseballPlayer", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Player | # | Team | rWAR w/tm . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 47, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:45593932_0_6869375743660252130_Scientist:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:45593932_0_6869375743660252130_Scientist", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Scientist", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Laureate | Country | Rationale . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 48, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:45593932_0_6869375743660252130_Scientist:Rationale", "label": "Rationale", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:45593932_0_6869375743660252130_Scientist", "desc": "Work, historic event, etc that the subject is known for. Applies to Person, Organization, ConcentrationCamp, etc", "table_name": "Scientist", "groundtruth_response": "known for : Work, historic event, etc that the subject is known for. Applies to Person, Organization, ConcentrationCamp, etc", "input_prompt": "Column name: Rationale . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Laureate | Country | Rationale . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 49, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21362676_0_6854186738074119688_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21362676_0_6854186738074119688_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 50, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21362676_0_6854186738074119688_Film:Director(s)", "label": "Director(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21362676_0_6854186738074119688_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 51, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:52299421_0_4473286348258170200_Country:GDP", "label": "GDP", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:52299421_0_4473286348258170200_Country", "desc": "The nominal gross domestic product of a country (not per capita).", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "gross domestic product (GDP) : The nominal gross domestic product of a country (not per capita).", "input_prompt": "Column name: GDP . [SEP] Other column names: 1998 Data Country | GDP Per Capita | GDP Growth Rate | GDP | Inflation | Population | Popul. Growth | Infant Mortality . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 52, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:26310680_0_5150772059999313798_Currency:ALPHABETIC CODE", "label": "ALPHABETIC CODE", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:26310680_0_5150772059999313798_Currency", "desc": "ISO 4217 currency designators.", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "currency code : ISO 4217 currency designators.", "input_prompt": "Column name: ALPHABETIC CODE . [SEP] Other column names: ENTITY | CURRENCY | ALPHABETIC CODE | NUMERIC CODE . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 53, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:26310680_0_5150772059999313798_Currency:NUMERIC CODE", "label": "NUMERIC CODE", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:26310680_0_5150772059999313798_Currency", "desc": "Superproperty for any designation (string, integer as string) that is meant to identify an entity within the context of a system", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "code : Superproperty for any designation (string, integer as string) that is meant to identify an entity within the context of a system", "input_prompt": "Column name: NUMERIC CODE . [SEP] Other column names: ENTITY | CURRENCY | ALPHABETIC CODE | NUMERIC CODE . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 54, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:93702496_0_39013305210829591_Company:Founders", "label": "Founders", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:93702496_0_39013305210829591_Company", "desc": "Ein Gr\u00fcnder oder Gr\u00fcndungsmitglied einer Organisation, Religion oder eines Ortes.", "table_name": "Company", "groundtruth_response": "founder : Ein Gr\u00fcnder oder Gr\u00fcndungsmitglied einer Organisation, Religion oder eines Ortes.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Founders . [SEP] Other column names: Rank | Company | Industry | Founders | Revenue Per Year | Revenue Per Second . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 55, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_6_8221428333921653560_VideoGame:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_6_8221428333921653560_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 56, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_6_8221428333921653560_VideoGame:Genre", "label": "Genre", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_6_8221428333921653560_VideoGame", "desc": "The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "genre : The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Genre . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 57, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_6_8221428333921653560_VideoGame:Platform(s)", "label": "Platform(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_6_8221428333921653560_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: Platform(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 58, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_6_8221428333921653560_VideoGame:Developer(s)", "label": "Developer(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_6_8221428333921653560_VideoGame", "desc": "Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "developer : Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Developer(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 59, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:84675086_0_6386416780680710863_Bird:Genus", "label": "Genus", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:84675086_0_6386416780680710863_Bird", "desc": "A rank in the classification of organisms, below family and above species; a taxon at that rank", "table_name": "Bird", "groundtruth_response": "genus : A rank in the classification of organisms, below family and above species; a taxon at that rank", "input_prompt": "Column name: Genus . [SEP] Other column names: Common Name | Genus | Species | IUCN . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 60, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:35188621_0_6058553107571275232_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:35188621_0_6058553107571275232_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 61, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:35188621_0_6058553107571275232_Film:Director(s)", "label": "Director(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:35188621_0_6058553107571275232_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 62, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:89511064_0_2199624509082573904_Country:Continent", "label": "Continent", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:89511064_0_2199624509082573904_Country", "desc": "links a country to the continent it belongs", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "continent : links a country to the continent it belongs", "input_prompt": "Column name: Continent . [SEP] Other column names: Continent | Region | Country | Capital | FIPS | ISO (2) | ISO (3) | ISO (No) | Internet | Note . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 63, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:89511064_0_2199624509082573904_Country:ISO (2)", "label": "ISO (2)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:89511064_0_2199624509082573904_Country", "desc": "defines codes for the names of countries, dependent territories, and special areas of geographical interest", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "ISO 3166-1 code : defines codes for the names of countries, dependent territories, and special areas of geographical interest", "input_prompt": "Column name: ISO (2) . [SEP] Other column names: Continent | Region | Country | Capital | FIPS | ISO (2) | ISO (3) | ISO (No) | Internet | Note . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 64, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:89511064_0_2199624509082573904_Country:ISO (3)", "label": "ISO (3)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:89511064_0_2199624509082573904_Country", "desc": "defines codes for the names of countries, dependent territories, and special areas of geographical interest", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "ISO 3166-1 code : defines codes for the names of countries, dependent territories, and special areas of geographical interest", "input_prompt": "Column name: ISO (3) . [SEP] Other column names: Continent | Region | Country | Capital | FIPS | ISO (2) | ISO (3) | ISO (No) | Internet | Note . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 65, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:53822652_0_5767892317858575530_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:53822652_0_5767892317858575530_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Date | Movie | Year | Director . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 66, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:53822652_0_5767892317858575530_Film:Director", "label": "Director", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:53822652_0_5767892317858575530_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director . [SEP] Other column names: Date | Movie | Year | Director . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 67, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21585935_0_294037497010176843_Airport:State", "label": "State", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21585935_0_294037497010176843_Airport", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Airport", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: State . [SEP] Other column names: Code | Airport Name | City | State . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 68, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:39759273_0_1427898308030295194_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:39759273_0_1427898308030295194_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: N | Title | Year | Director | IMDB Rating | IMDB Votes . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 69, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:39759273_0_1427898308030295194_Film:Director", "label": "Director", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:39759273_0_1427898308030295194_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director . [SEP] Other column names: N | Title | Year | Director | IMDB Rating | IMDB Votes . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 70, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame:Publisher", "label": "Publisher", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame", "desc": "Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "publisher : Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "input_prompt": "Column name: Publisher . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Cost | Size . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 71, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame:North America", "label": "North America", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: North America . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Cost | Size . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 72, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame:Europe", "label": "Europe", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Europe . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Cost | Size . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 73, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame:Japan", "label": "Japan", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Japan . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Cost | Size . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 74, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame:Cost", "label": "Cost", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame", "desc": "Cost of building an ArchitecturalStructure, Ship, etc", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "cost ($) : Cost of building an ArchitecturalStructure, Ship, etc", "input_prompt": "Column name: Cost . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Cost | Size . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 75, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame:Size", "label": "Size", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:22864497_0_8632623712684511496_VideoGame", "desc": "size of a file or software", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "size (B) : size of a file or software", "input_prompt": "Column name: Size . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Cost | Size . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 76, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:46671561_0_6122315295162029872_VideoGame:Genre", "label": "Genre", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:46671561_0_6122315295162029872_VideoGame", "desc": "The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "genre : The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Genre . [SEP] Other column names: Game | Genre | Platform | Release . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 77, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:46671561_0_6122315295162029872_VideoGame:Platform", "label": "Platform", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:46671561_0_6122315295162029872_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: Platform . [SEP] Other column names: Game | Genre | Platform | Release . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 78, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:46671561_0_6122315295162029872_VideoGame:Release", "label": "Release", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:46671561_0_6122315295162029872_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Release . [SEP] Other column names: Game | Genre | Platform | Release . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 79, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:98312357_0_6395417306876145729_Monarch:Spouse", "label": "Spouse", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:98312357_0_6395417306876145729_Monarch", "desc": "the person they are married to", "table_name": "Monarch", "groundtruth_response": "spouse : the person they are married to", "input_prompt": "Column name: Spouse . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Reign | Full Name | Family | Spouse . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 80, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:90593344_0_8311455501234425088_Mountain:Height (m)", "label": "Height (m)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:90593344_0_8311455501234425088_Mountain", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: Height (m) . [SEP] Other column names: Number | Fell Name | Height (m) | Height (Ft) | GPS reference | Guide | Steve | Justine | Emily | Sophie | Diva . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 81, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:90593344_0_8311455501234425088_Mountain:Height (Ft)", "label": "Height (Ft)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:90593344_0_8311455501234425088_Mountain", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: Height (Ft) . [SEP] Other column names: Number | Fell Name | Height (m) | Height (Ft) | GPS reference | Guide | Steve | Justine | Emily | Sophie | Diva . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 82, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_0_3859283110041832023_Country:Government", "label": "Government", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_0_3859283110041832023_Country", "desc": "broadly, the type of structure of its government", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "government type : broadly, the type of structure of its government", "input_prompt": "Column name: Government . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Date | Previous Names | Capital | Government | Languages . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 83, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_0_3859283110041832023_Country:Languages", "label": "Languages", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_0_3859283110041832023_Country", "desc": "Use dc:language for literal, language for object", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "language : Use dc:language for literal, language for object", "input_prompt": "Column name: Languages . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Date | Previous Names | Capital | Government | Languages . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 84, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame:Platform", "label": "Platform", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: Platform . [SEP] Other column names: Pos | Game | Platform | Year | Genre | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Rest of World | Global . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 85, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Pos | Game | Platform | Year | Genre | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Rest of World | Global . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 86, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame:Genre", "label": "Genre", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame", "desc": "The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "genre : The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Genre . [SEP] Other column names: Pos | Game | Platform | Year | Genre | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Rest of World | Global . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 87, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame:Publisher", "label": "Publisher", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame", "desc": "Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "publisher : Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "input_prompt": "Column name: Publisher . [SEP] Other column names: Pos | Game | Platform | Year | Genre | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Rest of World | Global . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 88, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame:North America", "label": "North America", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: North America . [SEP] Other column names: Pos | Game | Platform | Year | Genre | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Rest of World | Global . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 89, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame:Europe", "label": "Europe", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Europe . [SEP] Other column names: Pos | Game | Platform | Year | Genre | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Rest of World | Global . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 90, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame:Japan", "label": "Japan", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:57938705_0_8737506792349461963_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Japan . [SEP] Other column names: Pos | Game | Platform | Year | Genre | Publisher | North America | Europe | Japan | Rest of World | Global . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 91, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68442591_0_8506821153001360777_Hospital:Board", "label": "Board", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68442591_0_8506821153001360777_Hospital", "desc": "Used as if meaning: owned by, has as its owner", "table_name": "Hospital", "groundtruth_response": "owner : Used as if meaning: owned by, has as its owner", "input_prompt": "Column name: Board . [SEP] Other column names: Site | Board | Child Health | Obs & Gyn | Psych | Med | Surg . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 92, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:36102169_0_7739454799295072814_VideoGame:Platform", "label": "Platform", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:36102169_0_7739454799295072814_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: Platform . [SEP] Other column names: Platform | Developer | Game Title | Units Sold (in millions) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 93, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:36102169_0_7739454799295072814_VideoGame:Developer", "label": "Developer", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:36102169_0_7739454799295072814_VideoGame", "desc": "Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "developer : Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Developer . [SEP] Other column names: Platform | Developer | Game Title | Units Sold (in millions) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 94, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:7929299_0_3253718003116029649_Airport:State", "label": "State", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:7929299_0_3253718003116029649_Airport", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Airport", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: State . [SEP] Other column names: Code | Airport Name | City | State . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 95, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:41336118_0_4331895026409635103_Company:Sales ($bil)", "label": "Sales ($bil)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:41336118_0_4331895026409635103_Company", "desc": "This property holds an intermediate node of the type Sales.", "table_name": "Company", "groundtruth_response": "sales : This property holds an intermediate node of the type Sales.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Sales ($bil) . [SEP] Other column names: Company | Country | Industry | Sales ($bil) | Profits ($bil) | Assets ($bil) | Market Value ($bil) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 96, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:41336118_0_4331895026409635103_Company:Assets ($bil)", "label": "Assets ($bil)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:41336118_0_4331895026409635103_Company", "desc": "Assets and liabilities are part of a companis balance sheet. In financial accounting, assets are economic resources. Anything tangible or intangible that is capable of being owned or controlled to produce value and that is held to have positive economic value is considered an asset.", "table_name": "Company", "groundtruth_response": "assets ($) : Assets and liabilities are part of a companis balance sheet. In financial accounting, assets are economic resources. Anything tangible or intangible that is capable of being owned or controlled to produce value and that is held to have positive economic value is considered an asset.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Assets ($bil) . [SEP] Other column names: Company | Country | Industry | Sales ($bil) | Profits ($bil) | Assets ($bil) | Market Value ($bil) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 97, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:55961337_0_6548713781034932742_Currency:Alphabetic code", "label": "Alphabetic code", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:55961337_0_6548713781034932742_Currency", "desc": "ISO 4217 currency designators.", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "currency code : ISO 4217 currency designators.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Alphabetic code . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 98, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:55961337_0_6548713781034932742_Currency:Numeric code", "label": "Numeric code", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:55961337_0_6548713781034932742_Currency", "desc": "Superproperty for any designation (string, integer as string) that is meant to identify an entity within the context of a system", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "code : Superproperty for any designation (string, integer as string) that is meant to identify an entity within the context of a system", "input_prompt": "Column name: Numeric code . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 99, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:55961337_0_6548713781034932742_Currency:Symbol", "label": "Symbol", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:55961337_0_6548713781034932742_Currency", "desc": "HUGO Gene Symbol", "table_name": "Currency", "groundtruth_response": "Symbol : HUGO Gene Symbol", "input_prompt": "Column name: Symbol . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Currency | Alphabetic code | Numeric code | Symbol | Subdivision . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 100, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:53583534_0_503521622577229691_Building:Stadt", "label": "Stadt", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:53583534_0_503521622577229691_Building", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Building", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Stadt . [SEP] Other column names: Dauer | Geb?udename | Stadt | Etagen | H?he . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 101, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:53583534_0_503521622577229691_Building:H?he", "label": "H?he", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:53583534_0_503521622577229691_Building", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Building", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: H?he . [SEP] Other column names: Dauer | Geb?udename | Stadt | Etagen | H?he . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 102, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:8468806_0_4382447409703007384_Lake:Staat(en)", "label": "Staat(en)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:8468806_0_4382447409703007384_Lake", "desc": "The country where the thing is located.", "table_name": "Lake", "groundtruth_response": "country : The country where the thing is located.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Staat(en) . [SEP] Other column names: Rang | Name | Staat(en) | Fl\u00e4che-(km2) | L\u00e4nge-(km) | Max.-Tiefe-(m) | Volumen-(km?) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 103, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:8468806_0_4382447409703007384_Lake:Max.-Tiefe-(m)", "label": "Max.-Tiefe-(m)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:8468806_0_4382447409703007384_Lake", "desc": "Is a measure of the distance between a reference height and a point underneath. The exact meaning for a place is unclear. If possible, use  or  to be unambiguous.", "table_name": "Lake", "groundtruth_response": "depth (\u03bc) : Is a measure of the distance between a reference height and a point underneath. The exact meaning for a place is unclear. If possible, use  or  to be unambiguous.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Max.-Tiefe-(m) . [SEP] Other column names: Rang | Name | Staat(en) | Fl\u00e4che-(km2) | L\u00e4nge-(km) | Max.-Tiefe-(m) | Volumen-(km?) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 104, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:75367212_2_2745466355267233390_VideoGame:Developer(s)", "label": "Developer(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:75367212_2_2745466355267233390_VideoGame", "desc": "Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "developer : Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Developer(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Developer(s) | Publisher(s) | Release Date | ESRB . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 105, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:75367212_2_2745466355267233390_VideoGame:Publisher(s)", "label": "Publisher(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:75367212_2_2745466355267233390_VideoGame", "desc": "Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "publisher : Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "input_prompt": "Column name: Publisher(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Developer(s) | Publisher(s) | Release Date | ESRB . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 106, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:75367212_2_2745466355267233390_VideoGame:Release Date", "label": "Release Date", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:75367212_2_2745466355267233390_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Release Date . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Developer(s) | Publisher(s) | Release Date | ESRB . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 107, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:16949304_0_2573050770332101882_Hospital:Director", "label": "Director", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:16949304_0_2573050770332101882_Hospital", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Hospital", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director . [SEP] Other column names: Hospital | Hospital ID | Director | Supervisor(s) of training | Contact . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 108, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:11833461_1_3811022039809817402_VideoGame:Publisher", "label": "Publisher", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:11833461_1_3811022039809817402_VideoGame", "desc": "Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "publisher : Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "input_prompt": "Column name: Publisher . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | EU Release Date | AU Release Date | PEGI | ACB . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 109, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:11833461_1_3811022039809817402_VideoGame:EU Release Date", "label": "EU Release Date", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:11833461_1_3811022039809817402_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: EU Release Date . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | EU Release Date | AU Release Date | PEGI | ACB . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 110, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:11833461_1_3811022039809817402_VideoGame:AU Release Date", "label": "AU Release Date", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:11833461_1_3811022039809817402_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: AU Release Date . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Publisher | EU Release Date | AU Release Date | PEGI | ACB . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 111, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:12183399_0_6725061928072492226_Country:Currency Code", "label": "Currency Code", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:12183399_0_6725061928072492226_Country", "desc": "ISO 4217 currency designators.", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "currency code : ISO 4217 currency designators.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Currency Code . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Country Code (3-character) | Country Code (2-character) | Currency | Currency Code . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 112, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_2_4773219892816395776_VideoGame:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_2_4773219892816395776_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 113, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_2_4773219892816395776_VideoGame:Genre", "label": "Genre", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_2_4773219892816395776_VideoGame", "desc": "The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "genre : The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Genre . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 114, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_2_4773219892816395776_VideoGame:Platform(s)", "label": "Platform(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_2_4773219892816395776_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: Platform(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 115, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_2_4773219892816395776_VideoGame:Developer(s)", "label": "Developer(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_2_4773219892816395776_VideoGame", "desc": "Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "developer : Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Developer(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 116, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:86297395_0_6919201319699354263_Country:Land area", "label": "Land area", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:86297395_0_6919201319699354263_Country", "desc": "The area of the thing in square meters.", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "area (m2) : The area of the thing in square meters.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Land area . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Land area | GDP nominal (US$M) | Per capita GDP (US$) | Population | Government | Conscription . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 117, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:86297395_0_6919201319699354263_Country:GDP nominal (US$M)", "label": "GDP nominal (US$M)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:86297395_0_6919201319699354263_Country", "desc": "The nominal gross domestic product of a country (not per capita).", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "gross domestic product (GDP) : The nominal gross domestic product of a country (not per capita).", "input_prompt": "Column name: GDP nominal (US$M) . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Land area | GDP nominal (US$M) | Per capita GDP (US$) | Population | Government | Conscription . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 118, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:86297395_0_6919201319699354263_Country:Government", "label": "Government", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:86297395_0_6919201319699354263_Country", "desc": "broadly, the type of structure of its government", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "government type : broadly, the type of structure of its government", "input_prompt": "Column name: Government . [SEP] Other column names: Country | Land area | GDP nominal (US$M) | Per capita GDP (US$) | Population | Government | Conscription . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 119, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:24142265_0_4577466141408796359_VideoGame:System", "label": "System", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:24142265_0_4577466141408796359_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: System . [SEP] Other column names: Rank | Was | Peak | Days on Chart | System | Game . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 120, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:47709681_0_4437772923903322343_VideoGame:Release", "label": "Release", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:47709681_0_4437772923903322343_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Release . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Category | Rating | Release . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 121, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21245481_0_8730460088443117515_Lake:State/Province", "label": "State/Province", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:21245481_0_8730460088443117515_Lake", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Lake", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: State/Province . [SEP] Other column names: State/Province | Lake Name | File Size . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 122, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_12_251152470253168163_VideoGame:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_12_251152470253168163_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 123, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_12_251152470253168163_VideoGame:Genre", "label": "Genre", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_12_251152470253168163_VideoGame", "desc": "The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "genre : The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Genre . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 124, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_12_251152470253168163_VideoGame:Platform(s)", "label": "Platform(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_12_251152470253168163_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: Platform(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 125, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_12_251152470253168163_VideoGame:Developer(s)", "label": "Developer(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_12_251152470253168163_VideoGame", "desc": "Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "developer : Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Developer(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 126, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:1146722_1_7558140036342906956_Mountain:ALT (m)", "label": "ALT (m)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:1146722_1_7558140036342906956_Mountain", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: ALT (m) . [SEP] Other column names: PEAK | RANKING | MAP | GUIDE | GRID REF | ALT (ft) | ALT (m) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 127, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:30166286_0_1837439231599898748_Scientist:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:30166286_0_1837439231599898748_Scientist", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Scientist", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Prize | Year | Winner1 | Winner2 | Winner3 . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 128, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_13_8724394428539174350_VideoGame:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_13_8724394428539174350_VideoGame", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 129, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_13_8724394428539174350_VideoGame:Genre", "label": "Genre", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_13_8724394428539174350_VideoGame", "desc": "The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "genre : The genre of the thing (music group, film, etc.)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Genre . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 130, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_13_8724394428539174350_VideoGame:Platform(s)", "label": "Platform(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_13_8724394428539174350_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: Platform(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 131, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_13_8724394428539174350_VideoGame:Developer(s)", "label": "Developer(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:29414811_13_8724394428539174350_VideoGame", "desc": "Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "developer : Developer of a Work (Artwork, Book, Software) or Building (Hotel, Skyscraper)", "input_prompt": "Column name: Developer(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Year | Game | Genre | Platform(s) | Developer(s) . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 132, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:19654359_0_3020273135042459469_Airport:State", "label": "State", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:19654359_0_3020273135042459469_Airport", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Airport", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: State . [SEP] Other column names: Code | Airport Name | City | State . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 133, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:77694908_0_6083291340991074532_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:77694908_0_6083291340991074532_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 134, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:77694908_0_6083291340991074532_Film:Director(s)", "label": "Director(s)", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:77694908_0_6083291340991074532_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director(s) . [SEP] Other column names: Fans' Rank | Title | Year | Director(s) | Overall Rank . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 135, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:91959037_0_7907661684242014480_VideoGame:System", "label": "System", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:91959037_0_7907661684242014480_VideoGame", "desc": "some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "computing platform : some sort of hardware architecture or software framework, that allows this software to run", "input_prompt": "Column name: System . [SEP] Other column names: # | Titel | System | Reviews | Durchschnitt . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 136, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_5_2067037721454758189_Country:Government", "label": "Government", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_5_2067037721454758189_Country", "desc": "broadly, the type of structure of its government", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "government type : broadly, the type of structure of its government", "input_prompt": "Column name: Government . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Date | Previous Names | Capital | Government | Languages . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 137, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_5_2067037721454758189_Country:Languages", "label": "Languages", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:68779923_5_2067037721454758189_Country", "desc": "Use dc:language for literal, language for object", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "language : Use dc:language for literal, language for object", "input_prompt": "Column name: Languages . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Date | Previous Names | Capital | Government | Languages . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 138, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:11599512_1_280388135214354946_Country:Endroit", "label": "Endroit", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:11599512_1_280388135214354946_Country", "desc": "The regin where the thing is located or is connected to.", "table_name": "Country", "groundtruth_response": "region : The regin where the thing is located or is connected to.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Endroit . [SEP] Other column names: A | Nom en anglais | Endroit | Capitale | Heure . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 139, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:98929678_0_3700213490979945526_Lake:Basin countries", "label": "Basin countries", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:98929678_0_3700213490979945526_Lake", "desc": "The country where the thing is located.", "table_name": "Lake", "groundtruth_response": "country : The country where the thing is located.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Basin countries . [SEP] Other column names: Lake | Location | Basin countries | Residence time . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 140, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:52208141_2_5171684379987586712_Museum:Stadt", "label": "Stadt", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:52208141_2_5171684379987586712_Museum", "desc": "The location of the thing.", "table_name": "Museum", "groundtruth_response": "location : The location of the thing.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Stadt . [SEP] Other column names: RANG | Museum | Stadt | Facebook-Fans . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 141, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:4501311_8_8306082458935575308_VideoGame:Publisher", "label": "Publisher", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:4501311_8_8306082458935575308_VideoGame", "desc": "Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "publisher : Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "input_prompt": "Column name: Publisher . [SEP] Other column names: Rank | Title | Category | Publisher . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 142, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:14311244_0_7604843865524657408_Mountain:HEIGHT IN METERS", "label": "HEIGHT IN METERS", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:14311244_0_7604843865524657408_Mountain", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Mountain", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: HEIGHT IN METERS . [SEP] Other column names: MOUNTAIN | HEIGHT IN METERS | RANGE | CONQUERED ON . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 143, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:50245608_0_871275842592178099_Film:Year", "label": "Year", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:50245608_0_871275842592178099_Film", "desc": "Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "release date : Release date of a Work or another product (eg Aircraft or other MeansOfTransportation", "input_prompt": "Column name: Year . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Year | Media Type | Director | Writer | Length | Matting . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 144, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:50245608_0_871275842592178099_Film:Director", "label": "Director", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:50245608_0_871275842592178099_Film", "desc": "A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "film director : A film director is a person who directs the making of a film.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Director . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Year | Media Type | Director | Writer | Length | Matting . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 145, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:50245608_0_871275842592178099_Film:Length", "label": "Length", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:50245608_0_871275842592178099_Film", "desc": "The duration of the item (movie, audio recording, event, etc.) in ISO 8601 date format", "table_name": "Film", "groundtruth_response": "duration (s) : The duration of the item (movie, audio recording, event, etc.) in ISO 8601 date format", "input_prompt": "Column name: Length . [SEP] Other column names: Title | Year | Media Type | Director | Writer | Length | Matting . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 146, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:45533669_1_7463037039059239824_RadioStation:Editeur", "label": "Editeur", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:45533669_1_7463037039059239824_RadioStation", "desc": "Used as if meaning: owned by, has as its owner", "table_name": "RadioStation", "groundtruth_response": "owner : Used as if meaning: owned by, has as its owner", "input_prompt": "Column name: Editeur . [SEP] Other column names: Service | Editeur | Pays . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 147, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:73242003_5_4847571983313033360_VideoGame:Publisher", "label": "Publisher", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:73242003_5_4847571983313033360_VideoGame", "desc": "Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "table_name": "VideoGame", "groundtruth_response": "publisher : Publisher of a work. For literal (string) use dc:publisher; for object (URL) use publisher", "input_prompt": "Column name: Publisher . [SEP] Other column names: Rank | Title | Category | Publisher . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 148, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:3887681_0_7938589465814037992_Lake:H?he", "label": "H?he", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:3887681_0_7938589465814037992_Lake", "desc": "average elevation above the sea level", "table_name": "Lake", "groundtruth_response": "elevation (\u03bc) : average elevation above the sea level", "input_prompt": "Column name: H?he . [SEP] Other column names: Name | H?he | Typ | Baujahr | See | Kanton . [SEP] Column description:"}
{"uuid": 149, "id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:18422942_0_3659164506677528063_Work:Artist", "label": "Artist", "table_id": "t2dv2:dbpedia:18422942_0_3659164506677528063_Work", "desc": "The performer or creator of the musical work.", "table_name": "Work", "groundtruth_response": "performer : The performer or creator of the musical work.", "input_prompt": "Column name: Artist . [SEP] Other column names: Name | Artist | Genre . [SEP] Column description:"}
